

+612-203-9775



wrightkellyjo@gmail.com



a A passion for problem solving.

KELLY WRIGHT

From simple to complex, I love collaborating with a team to find the root cause and design & develop ideal solutions that are easy to use.

Victoria, Minnesota



# PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

I'm a Learning & Development professional with over 4 years of experiences and a strong passion for process improvement and implementation. I'm known for making the complex simple, designing user friendly experiences for my team, and helping remove roadblocks when they occur. I love exploring technology and finding new ways to utilize what we already have.

# **EDUCATION**

#### **Metropolitan State University**

Bachelor's Degree in Marketing 2009

#### Normandale Commuunity College

Associate Degree 2007

### SKILLS

- Content & Knowledge Management
- Agile Project Management
- Exceptional communication and interpersonal skills
- Ability to work independently and as part of a team
- Detail-oriented and able to handle multiple tasks simultaneously
- Experience in managing budgets and handling financial documents

# CERTIFICATIONS

#### University Of Minnesota - edX

Ux/UI Bootcamp 2024

#### ServiceNow

Certified System Admin (CSA) 2024

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### **Substitute Teacher**

La Academia Dual Immersion Elementary School | 2023 - Present

- Substitute Teacher assigned to La Academis Elementary 3 days a week.
- Provide classroom teacher coverage for all teacher within the building, as well as sped paraprofessionals coverage supporting students with unique learning needs.

## ServiceNow Sr. Analyst - HRSD

RSM US, LLC | 2022 - 2023

- Lead the design, development & implementation of HRSD (Human Resources ServiceNow) including the use of SN's Employee Center as the new interface for team members to engage with HR.
- Prepared and distributed
- Coordinated

# Operations Sr. Associate \_ Learning & Professional Development

RSM US, LLC | 2017 - 2022

- Assisted executive secretary in managing and coordinating schedules, meetings, and travel arrangements for senior executives
- Provided administrative support,